so on the I just got off the make a
conversation and then had a shower and I
just love this group I feel like it
rejuvenates my soul every time we had
the topic of a coronavirus and although
there were periods that were definitely
I felt fear in my body and stress
there was also when I left the
conversation I had a internalized sense
of abundance as I always do at this
group this conversation is part of my
life and part of the world included
during the conversation we were talking
about whoo and this idea of like the
whoo that proves itself as you go and
one of the participants said that part
of possibly putting these conversations
online is that it's not about them going
viral and having everyone watch them
it's about the right person finding it
and watching it and in my mind before
the right person like the person they
can help it succeed the person but it's
not that it's the person it sparked
something inside of the person that it
just adds a little bit to their life
right if it makes one person's day a
little bit better or life a little bit
better at the right moment in time
that's the weird woo that is actually
what we should be going after or not
going after just allowing and so when I
try to filter my content try to make it
so that it's something that more people
will understand it'll resonate with more
people it's okay
and it's also okay not to do that
because the right person and I've said
that before but the definition of the
right person has altered in my mind from
the right person for the project to the
right person for the future the right
person for their future it just to trust
that the right people will hear it and I
was already doing that for the project
but it's coming at it from a little dip
point we're like even if that never
happens and materializes the right
person will hear it cuz I know that has
been the case for me like this morning
watching Bret Weinstein's talk on the
fourth frontier and I'm doing I doing a
video on it because the last piece of it
was just so beautiful which was this
orchestrated engineered stable abundance
and the definition of that that we need
this sense of living in a world that is
both abundant and safe and that it's
looking out for us looking after us that
we feel from that state we can be better
human beings and we talking through this
coronavirus where that's part of it is
that we're not showing up as our best
selves and we're scared and we have
disinformation and we have and ending on
this engineered internal abundance what
I would I'm it's coming up for me is we
can't start from a place of a resources
being abundant but we can start from our
relationships our abundance our
emotional capacity is abundant and
engineer that stable abundance how can
we give everyone connection and
emotional access to emotional tools or
and those are the things we can create
together we can create the system that
helps everyone have a weekly group of
people they can talk to orchestrate the
system that allows people to find
exactly the type of people that are
their people and so from the one random
person which is not random I talk to her
every week but if I didn't have this and
didn't have her I wouldn't have gotten
that piece of of woo from her and I
wouldn't be taking it into my beam to
put out into the world I'm just gonna
put out more content you're welcome
because it's the right person it's not
about having tens of thousands of
subscribers it's about one person taking
it and running with it and creating
something that I can envision it's how
we're interconnected in all of these
ways that aren't broadcast they're nodes
there and we're all that we can all have
a hundred thousand subscribers we all
can have a hundred we all look and talk
to one another we all can show up and
have conversations that matter to us as
individuals and that will create a
increased sense of stabilized abundance
so we're able to act from a better place
that's then able to create the resource
abundance and the saftey abundance that
we need to become better and better
people and stay more stable unstable
environment so that is today's video
Thanks